nandosearch.com 2002-11-28

# The Nando Times: Privacy

|   
---  
N E W S  
Front Page  
Top Story  
Nation  
World  
Sports  
Business  
Technology  
Politics  
Opinions  
Health & Science  
Entertainment  
Weird News  
Special Reports  
M E M B E R S  
Create Account  
Lost Password  
Member Help  
F E A T U R E S  
Newsletters  
News Galleries  
News Watcher  
News Forums  
Today In Photos  
Today In History  
Horoscope  
S E R V I C E S  
Weather  
Classifieds  
Nando Mail  
| 

* * *

**Nando Media's Privacy Policy** Nando Media has a firm commitment to privacy. We take your privacy concerns seriously and want to make every effort to address them. That is why we have adopted the following policy, which explains our position on information-gathering and disclosure. 

**Your Personal Information**

From time to time, we will ask for information that personally identifies you, as in our user surveys or registration for Nando Media services such as e-mail, forums, or promotions. We use this information to operate Nando Media's services, provide you with the highest quality services and offer you opportunities we think will be of interest. 

We will not disclose any personal information without your advance permission except when we believe the law requires us to do so or the disclosure is necessary to protect the rights or property of Nando Media, or as explained below or in our User Agreement. 

In order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers and others, we may disclose user information but only in a form that does not identify individual users. For example, we might disclose that a certain percentage of our users are male or within a certain age range. 

Occasionally, we may disclose personal information in other circumstances, but we will only do this if we have explained at the time we collect the information the purpose for which it will be disclosed. 

**Kids' Privacy**

Nando Media is particularly concerned with providing a safe online environment for kids. Therefore, in areas operated by Nando Media that are directed to kids or when we learn that a user is under the age of 13, we will ask for parental consent before collecting additional personal information about the child or allowing the child to use the Nando Media services to provide additional personal information. 

**Parental consent can be provided in two ways:**

**(1)** Send a fax copy of a completed [Parental Consent Form,](http://www.nandotimes.com/standing/parental/) including your signature, to the facsimile number provided on the Parental Consent Form (which will be provided in applicable areas on our site) 

**(2)** Call us at the telephone number provided on the [Parental Consent Form.](http://www.nandotimes.com/standing/parental/)

Nando Media will not knowingly disclose personal information about users under the age of 13 without prior parental consent, except as required by law. If for any reason you wish to access, update or remove information about your child or terminate your child's account, you may fax or call Nando Media at the numbers listed above or contact us through our [feedback page.](http://archive.nandotimes.com/links/feedback.html)

Nando Media strongly recommends parental supervision when a child uses the Internet, and particularly when a child enters a forum or uses e-mail. We also encourage parents to instruct their children not to give out personal information in these areas. 

**E-Commerce**

Nando Media hosts a number of online stores that sell a variety of goods and services. These stores may collect information from you such as your name, credit card number and other contact information. Nando Media does not collect, use or disclose this information nor does it own or control the stores or have responsibility for transactions made by those merchants. If you would like to know more about the information collected when you participate in e-commerce on or through this site, please contact the store merchants directly. 

**Ads**

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by Real Media, our Web advertising partner. Please [click here](http://www.realmedia.com/privacy.html) for more information on Real Media and its privacy policy. 

**Cookies**

A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Nando Media to recognize you each time you visit this site. Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Nando Media does not use cookies to collect personal information. Instead, they allow us to see which parts of our site you have used so that we can better serve you when you return to our site. Cookies may be used to provide you with information and special opportunities tailored to your interests. 

**Direct Mailings and "Opting Out"**

We may send you information about various products and services. If you don't want to receive this information, you can "opt out" by sending us an e-mail at webmaster@nandomedia.com and requesting that you not receive any of these of these offers. 

Registered users who did not opt-in upon registering will not receive promotional e-mails. 

**You Can Change Your Private Information at any Time**

Information you provide to Nando Media may be stored by us for an indefinite time. However, please feel free to change, update or delete this information at any time by sending a request through our [feedback page](http://archive.nandotimes.com/links/feedback.html).

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**

You should know that when you voluntarily disclose personal information on the Nando Media system (for example, in forums), that information can be collected and used by others and may result in unsolicited messages from other people. While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Nando Media and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition, our partners and other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Nando Media have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies. 

**Tell Us How We're Doing**

If you have any questions or comments about our policies, please contact us through our [feedback page.](http://www.nandotimes.com/links/feedback.html)

Copyright © 2002 Nando Media  
Do you have some [feedback](http://www.nandotimes.com/links/feedback.html) for the Nando Times staff?  

* * *

* * *

|
